<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="qt_intro_header">Thanks for installing NeverBeLate™!</string>
    <string name="qt_intro_message">Congratulations on the first step toward taking control of your schedule 
        and eliminating lateness in your professional and personal life.\n\nThis quick tour is simple 
        to use: swipe left and right to move between pages, and swipe up and down to scroll.\n\nNow swipe 
        to the next page to get started!</string>
    <string name="qt_skip_tour"><u>... or skip the tour.</u></string>
    
    <string name="qt_enable_header">Enabling NeverBeLate™</string>
    <string name="qt_enable_message_1">Turning on the NeverBeLate™ Advance Warning system is simple. On the main
        screen you will find a checkbox just the like the one below. Just check the box, and then rest easy knowing
        that NeverBeLate™ is working behind the scenes to keep you on time to all of your events.</string>
    <string name="qt_enable_message_2">Well, there is actually one more thing that NeverBeLate™ needs to
        work properly. Swipe to the next page to learn what it is!</string>
    
    <string name="qt_searchable_header">A Searchable Address</string>
    <string name="qt_searchable_message_1">The simplest definition for a searchable address is one that you can 
        search for in Google Maps. NeverBeLate™ requires each of your event locations to be a searchable address 
        so that it can determine travel distances and times correctly. Good examples are \"221b Baker Street, 
        London, UK\",  or if you\'re in a hurry, just \"Atlanta, GA\" or even \"77059\". A good tradeoff between 
        accuracy and speed of entry is to enter just the street address and the postal code, as shown  
        in the example below.</string>
    <string name="qt_where">Where</string>
    <string name="qt_sample_location">30 Rockefeller, 10112</string>
    <string name="qt_searchable_message_2">If you leave the location field of an event empty, NeverBeLate™ 
        will simply ignore it. Looks pretty easy, doesn\'t it?</string>
    
    <string name="qt_marked_header">Marked Locations</string>
    <string name="qt_marked_message_1">\"But what if I want to use both general locations and searchable 
        addresses in my calendar?\" Now you can! A new marked locations feature has been added to help spot the 
        searchable addresses amongst the bad ones. Enabling marked locations is simple: look in the Settings 
        menu to find the \"Only marked locations\" option shown below, and check the box.</string>
    <string name="qt_marked_message_2">Then start placing an asterisk or star (*) at the beginning of your 
        searchable event locations, just like this: \"*Atlanta, GA\". NeverBeLate™ will then only look for 
        the marked locations, and will ignore the rest. Next time a coworker invites you to a meeting in 
        \"Joe\'s office\", you won\'t be warned incorrectly.</string>
    
    <string name="qt_traffic_header">Check the Traffic</string>
    <string name="qt_traffic_message_1">One of the most powerful features of NeverBeLate™ is the instant opportunity
        to check the traffic between where you are now and where you need to be. When an Advance Warning 
        dialog pops up to warn you that it is time to leave for your next event, you will see a large green 
        button just like the one below.</string>
    <string name="qt_traffic_message_2">Press this button to view a colorful map showing the traffic in the 
        area. Your current location will be marked with a blue flag, and your event location will be marked with
        a red flag. The traffic will be color-coded just like in Google Maps. If the traffic is red, be sure 
        to leave as soon as possible!</string>
    
    <string name="qt_final_header">Just the Beginning</string>
    <string name="qt_final_message_1">These few steps cover just the basics of putting NeverBeLate™ to work for 
        you. I challenge you to explore the settings menu to discover new ways to adjust the performance of 
        NeverBeLate™ to fit your lifestyle and travel needs. You can adjust the travel method, the early arrival 
        time, and your preferred notification method, just to name a few.</string>
    <string name="qt_final_message_2">A good productivity app should help you get more done with less effort. 
        NeverBeLate™ is designed to be an indispensable tool that blends with your favorite calendar app 
        and makes sticking to your schedule an effortless task. Test it for yourself: go create a test event 
        in your calendar, and let NeverBeLate™ take care of the reminder!</string>
    <string name="qt_finish_button">Done</string>
</resources>