<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="whats_new_title">What\'s new in NeverBeLate™</string>
    <integer name="whats_new_version">15</integer>
    <string name="whats_new_message">Version 1.1_build-17:\n\nFixed a bug to prevent force-closes associated 
        with a null user location (such as when all location providers are disabled). Also revised the Quick 
        Tour to make the setup process easier to understand.\n
        \nVersion 1.1_build-16:\n\nAdded the new Quick Tour! It will help you get 
        up and running quickly, and should answer some of the questions you may have about how to make 
        NeverBeLate™ work for you.\n
        \nVersion 1.0_build-15:\n\nMade the launcher screen scrollable to support 
        devices with smaller screens. If you have a small-screen device, and you find that another feature in 
        NeverBeLate™ does not fit properly on your screen, please send me some feedback to let me know!\n
        \nVersion 1.0_build-14:\n\nAdjusted the warning dialog text to include the early
        arrival parameter set by the user, and reduced the number of ads shown at the launcher screen.\n
        \nVersion 1.0_build-13:\n\nAdded a new Early Arrival parameter to the Settings
        menu. Set it for how early you wish to arrive at your destination, and NeverBeLate™ will account
        for that extra time when determining what time to alert you for your next event. The default Early Arrival
        value is five minutes.\n
        \nVersion 1.0_build-12:\n\nAdded the ability to mark events for NeverBeLate™
        to find by placing an asterisk or star (*) at the beginning of the event location. For example,
        \"*221b Baker Street, London, UK\" or \"*Houston, TX\". Now if a coworker invites you to a meeting 
        with a location of \"Conference Room 4b\", NeverBeLate™ will just ignore that event and will not 
        warn you incorrectly. To enable marked events, simply check the box labeled \"Only marked events\"
        in the Settings menu. Then start placing an asterisk or star (*) at the beginning of your searchable event locations.</string>
</resources>